<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator>
  <link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/tag/introduction/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
  <updated>2021-11-29T16:04:46-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://localhost:4000/blog/tag/introduction/feed.xml</id>

  
  
  

  
    <title type="html">Bryan Yu | </title>
  

  
    <subtitle>An immersive lifestyle and photography blog</subtitle>
  

  

  
    
      
    
      
    
  

  
  

  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">A Quick Introduction</title>
      <link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/a-quick-introduction" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Quick Introduction" />
      <published>2020-01-02T12:00:00-05:00</published>
      <updated>2020-01-02T12:00:00-05:00</updated>
      <id>http://localhost:4000/blog/a-quick-introduction</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/a-quick-introduction">&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone! My name is Bryan Yu, and this is officially my first post and website I have ever created.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a quick introduction, I am a Mathematics and Business Student at the University of Waterloo and Wilfrid Laurier University in Ontario, Canada. The main focuses of my academics are in Statistics and Finance. I know what you are thinking, how did a STEM student end up becoming a travel and fitness blog writer and photographer? Over the years, I have realized that my life is so much more than just my academics and professional work. I have a passion for fitness and exploring new places. From chasing sunsets and sunrises to exploring new cultures and cities worldwide, I love it all. This blog is just a small snippet of my adventures around the world and my fitness journey to becoming a healthier and more well-rounded person. Please feel free to peruse my writing and photography. I hope you can relive the happiest moments of my journey, and I can inspire you to travel and explore with me!&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>Bryan Yu</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="introduction" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">Hi everyone! My name is Bryan Yu, and this is officially my first post and website I have ever created.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
</feed>
